Summay Privacy Policy
=====================

Last Updated: February 16, 2022

‍

This is the Privacy Policy of the Sunsama.com website and any affiliated software and mobile applications (collectively, the “Site”), operated by Summay, Inc. (together with our affiliates and subsidiaries, “Summay”, “we”, “us”, “our” and terms of similar meaning) and our related products and services (collectively, the “Service” or “Services”). It describes the information that we collect from you as part of the normal operation of our Site, and how we use and disclose this information. All of the different forms of data, content, and information described below are collectively referred to as “information.”

By accepting the Privacy Policy in the registration process or by visiting and using the Site or the Services, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Service. Capitalized terms used but not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Service.

###### 1\. The Information We Collect And Store

We may collect and store the following information when running our Service:

Information You Provide.  We may collect personal information that can be used to contact or identify you, and may include information such as an individual’s name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, and payment or bank account details (“Personal Information”).

When you register an Account, we may collect some Personal Information, such as your name, your name, your phone number, a credit card or other billing information, your email address and postal addresses. The Site allows you to link your Third Party Accounts. We may use OAuth (as defined below), if available, to access Third Party Accounts in order to limit our collection of your passwords. “OAuth” is an open protocol for authorization, commonly used a way for users to log in to sites using their accounts with third-party services, such as Google or Microsoft, but without exposing their third-party-service passwords to such sites. For a Third Party Account that does not support OAuth, we will ask for your login credentials for such Third Party Account, which may include your email address and password. In all cases, we may collect your name and email address and the names and email addresses of your email contacts, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you create an Account using your login credentials from one of your Third Party Accounts, we may access and collect your name and email address and other Personal Information that your privacy settings on the Third Party Account permit us to access, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

When you invite others to join Summay, you provide us with certain contact information that allows us to send an invitation. We may also receive Personal Information through other users, for example if they have tried to give you access to a Summay account or refer Summay to you. It is your responsibility to ensure that your Personal Information is up-to-date.

Others’ Personal Information.  If you provide Personal Information about someone else, you must ensure and hereby agree that you are authorized to disclose that information to Summay and that, without Summay taking any further steps required by applicable data protection or privacy laws, Summay may collect, use and disclose such information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. You must take reasonable steps to ensure that the individual concerned is aware of and consents to the various matters detailed in this Privacy Policy, including the fact that that person’s Personal Information is being collected, the purposes for which that information is being collected, the intended recipients of that information, Summay’s identity, and how to contact Summay.

Sensitive Personal Information. You are prohibited from uploading any Sensitive Personal Information about yourself or others, as set forth in the Terms of Service.

Log Data.   When you use the Service, we may automatically record information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Services. This may include the Device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you select or search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata concerning your files, and other interactions with the Service.

Cookies and Tracking Technologies.   We also use technologies such as cookies, JavaScript, local storage (as defined below), pixel tags and scripts to collect information, provide a better user experience, and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your Device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service. “Local storage” is a way for a website to collect and store information “locally” (e.g., on the user’s device rather than on the website’s server) and then later retrieve it again. Local storage includes “localStorage” and “sessionStorage.” By using local storage, a user’s visits can, for example, be stored on their own computer, counted, and then given to us.

###### 2\. How We Use Personal Information

Personal Information. Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to better understand your needs and interests, (iv) to personalize and improve your experience, and (v) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of those communications, or update your account settings information.

Analytics.   We also collect some information (ourselves or using third party services) using logging and cookies, such as IP address, which can sometimes be correlated with Personal Information. We use this information for the above purposes and to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase our Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to verify users have the authorization needed for the Service to process their requests. We may use Highlight and Intercom for these purposes. To learn more about the privacy policy of Highlight, click [here](https://www.highlight.run/privacy). To learn more about the privacy policy of Intercom, click [here](https://www.intercom.com/legal/privacy).

Google Analytics. Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.

Facebook Pixel. Our website uses Facebook Pixel, a service which transmits website traffic data to Facebook's servers. We use reports provided by Facebook Pixel to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.

###### 3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

Your Use.  User Content that you provide to us may be shared with other Users that are connected to your Account. You can also use the Services to share your User Content with other third parties. For example, your calendar information may be integrated into your Account, and, if you are invited to attend a meeting, or if you invite others to attend a meeting, your meeting notes may automatically be posted to your calendar and so shared with the other meeting attendees (whether or not they are Account holders). Under no circumstances will we sell your Personal Information to third parties.

Service Providers, Business Partners and Others.   We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

Third Party Applications.   We may share your information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our Services through such an application. We are not responsible for what those parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Summay's Rights.   We may disclose to parties outside Summay information that you provide and that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Summay or its users; or (d) to protect Summay’s property rights.

Services's use of information received, and Services's transfer of information to any other app, from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use Requirements. You can learn more about how we utilize data from the Gmail API [here](https://help.sunsama.com/docs/privacy-notes)

Business Transfers.   If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your information, or if your information becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

Non-Private or Non-Personal Information.   We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.

###### 4\. Changing or Deleting Your Information

You can access and modify the Personal Information associated with your Account by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://sunsama.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please note that if you signed up using Third Party Account, you may have to access and modify the Personal Information associated with your Third Party Account in order to modify certain of the Personal Information associated with your Account. If you want us to delete your Personal Information and your Account, please delete your Account via sunsama.com/settings or contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://sunsama.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with your request. We will take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law.

###### 5\. Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your Account is active or as needed to provide you the Services. If you are a User and wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you Services, you may delete your account. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. Only the User may request that an Account be deleted.

###### 6\. Security

The security of your information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://sunsama.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

###### 7\. Our Policy Toward Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://sunsama.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will take steps to delete such information from our files.

###### 8\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://sunsama.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

###### 9\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time, and the most current version will be posted on our Site, so please check our Site regularly. We may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

‍
-

Help

Apps

Integrations

Team

Information

Cookie Preferences

© 2024 Summay, Inc.

[Designed by

](#)
